Guide to the Rice University Past Faculty and Staff records, 1961-1996 UA 008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1915-2003, 119315
  - Garrett, David L. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1982-1983; 167575 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Garrett, George P. - English, 1961-1962; 167577 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Garrett, M. Truett, Jr. - Chemistry, n.d.; 167576 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Garrison, Allen D. - Chemistry, 1925-1953; 167578 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Gary, John H., III - Naval Science (replaced by Dougal Cameron), 167579 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Gay, Col. Joseph M. - Military Science, 1972-1973; 167580 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - George, Stephen L. - Mathematical Sciences, 1971-1976; 167581 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Gerhardt, James H. - Political Science, 1967-1972; 167582 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Gerstel, Eva-Marie - French, 1963-1965; 167583 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Gersten, Stephen M. - Mathematics, 1964-1973; 167584 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Gessell, Thomas F. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1974-1982; 167585 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Gevritz, Joel L. - Geology, 1977-1978; 167586 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Ghali, Moheb - Economics, 1966-1967; 167587 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Ghosn, Abdel Hassan - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1981-1982; 167588 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Giacchetti, Claudine A. - French/Italian, 1980-1981; 167589 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Giannoni, Carlo B. - Philosophy, 1967-1981; 167590 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Gibson, Kathleen Rita - Anthropology, 1972-1976; 167591 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Giese, Robert P. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1983-1984; 167592 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Gila, Antonio - Spanish, 1971-1976; 167593 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Giles, James Bernard - Director of Admissions/Economics, 1947-1976; 167594 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Gilette, Robert Douglas - Chemical Engineering, 1977-1978; 167595 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Gilmartin, Kristine - Classics, 1966-1967; 167596 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Giovanetti, René - French, 1966-1967; 167597 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Glaeser, Donald H. - Electrical Engineering, 1974-1976; 167598 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Glaser, Leslie C. - Mathematics, 1964-1968; 167599 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Godfrey, H. Lee - Political Science, 1979-1982; 167600 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Godwin, James H. - Space Science, ca. 1971; 167601 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Goldwire, Henry C., Jr. - Space Science, 1968-1975; 167602 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Goldwyn, Roger M. - Electrical Engineering, 1963-1966; 167603 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Gorchs, Marta Lia - Spanish, 1976-1978; 167604 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Gorman, Donald V. - Naval Science (photograph), 1970-1973; 167605 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Gow, David John - Political Science, 1977-1981; 167606 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Graham, Martin - Electrical Engineering, 1961-1966; 167607 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Graham, Robin L. - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1977; 167608 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Green, Jeanette Kay - Biology, 1978-1980; 167609 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Gregory, Walton C. - Mathematical Sciences, 1973-1976; 167610 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Griffin, Patricia Peck - Political Science, 1972; 167611 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Griffis, LeVan - Mechanical Engineering, 1960-1963; 167612 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Griffith, Kenneth M. - Psychology, 1963; 167613 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Lopez-Grigera, Luisa - Spanish, 1972; 167614 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Grillo, Paul Jacques - Architecture, 1961-1963, 1965; 167615 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Guderian, Mack D. - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1982; 167616 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Gujer, Willi - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1979; 167617 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Gustafson, Donald F. - Philosophy, 1967-1968; 167618 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Hagelin, Lt. John - Naval Science, 1983; 167619 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Hahamis, Joanna - Physical Education, 1957-1967; 167620 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Hake, Evelyn - Biology, 1938-1972; 167621 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Hale, Elton Bernard - Managerial Studies, 1963-1983; 167622 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Hall, Arthur E. - Shepherd School of Music, 1954-1978; 167623 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Hall, Robert L. - History, 1981-1982; 167624 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Hammond, Brian Ralph - Biology, 1969-1975; 167625 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Hampton, Gary W. - Health and Physical Education, 1969-1980; 167626 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Hankamer, Jorge - Germanics, 1966-1967; 167627 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Hanks, Dorothy M. - German, 1972-1978; 167628 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Hanks, Milton - Civil Engineering, 1981; 167629 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Hannon, Aenne Gabriele - German and Russian, 1983; 167630 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Hanson, Alice Marie - Shepherd School of Music, 1977-1982; 167631 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Hardy, Heather Kay - Linguistics and Semiotics, 1982; 167632 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Hargreaves, J. K. - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1983; 167633 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Harkins, Carl Girvin - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1973-1984; 167634 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Harman, Thomas L. - Electrical Engineering, 1974-1983; 167635 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Harris, Diane S. - Biology, 1976-1978; 167636 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Harris, Gary A. - Mathematics, 1980-1981; 167637 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Harris, Scott A. - Political Science, 1976-1980; 167638 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Harrison, Boyd L. - Chemistry, 1973-1974; 167639 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Harris-Schenz, Beverly - German, 1979-1980; 167640 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Hart, William W. C. - Chemical Engineering, 1980; 167641 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Hartley, Craig - Electrical Engineering, 1972-1973; 167642 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Harvey, Charles M. - Mathematical Sciences, 1977-1978; 167643 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Hatfield, Lynn - Physics, 1967-1968; 167644 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Hattwick, Melvin S. - Commerce, 1968; 167645 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Hauge, Robert H. - Chemistry, 1972; 167646 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Haupt, Johannes R. - Germanics, 1967-1968; 167647 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Havel, James J. - Chemistry, 1972-1977; 167648 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Hayes, Edward F. - Chemistry, 1968-1978; 167649 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Heath, James Maguire - Classics (photograph), 1961-1966; 167910 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Hebert, Joel J. - Mechanical Engineering, 1969-1974; 167911 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Hedges, Adele Oglesbee - French, 1979; 167912 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Heimsath, Clovis Benton - Architecture, 1962-1965; 167913 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Heintz, Jean Georges - Religious Studies, 1982; 167914 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Helfferich, Friedrich G. - Chemical Engineering, 1980; 167917 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Hellums, Bonnie C. - Director of Student Activities and Personal Counselor, 1969-1975; 167918 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hellums, J. D. - Chemical Engineering, 1960-1998, 2003-2005; 167919 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Helt, Richard C. - Germanics, 1972-1978; 167920 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hendren, Philip A. - Architecture, 1970-1973; 167921 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Hendrickson, Bruce - Mechanical Engineering, 1962; 167922 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Henny, David C. - Naval Science, 1971-1973; 167923 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hermann, Gunther J. - Psychology, 1962-1963; 167924 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Herson, Jay H. - Mathematical Sciences, 1977-1981; 167925 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Hesson, James Loren - Health and Physical Education, 1980-1981; 167926 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Higginbotham, James B. - Commerce, 1969-1977; 167927 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Higginbotham, Sanford Wilson - History, 1961-1983; 167928 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Hill, Laurita Lyttleton - English, 1961-1962; 167929 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Hill, Thomas W. - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1976-1984; 167930 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Hills, H. Kent - Physics, 1973-1975; 167931 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hindman, Ross L. - Sociology, 1972; 167932 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Hiniker, Alice Ann - Psychology, 1979; 167933 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Hirschberg, Daniel - Electrical Engineering, 1975-1982; 167934 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Hitchens, Keith - History, 1965-1967; 167935 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Hodges, John Elton - Economics, 1947-1965; 167936 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hole, Frank - Anthropology and Sociology, 1961-1980; 167937 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Holibaugh, Ralph W. - Shepherd School of Music/Music Librarian, 1978-1982; 167938 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Hollingsworth, John Gressett - Mathematics, 1966-1967; 167939 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Hoobler, Raymond Taylor - Mathematics, 1972-1975; 167940 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Hopkins, Charles Adrian - Biology, 1962-1963; 167941 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Horning, Evan C. - Biochemistry, 1971-1978 [?]; 167942 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Houston, William Vermillion - Physics/University President, 1940-1968; 167943 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Howell, John K. - Architecture, 1974-1978; 167944 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Hrdy, Sarah Blaffer - Anthropology, 1981; 167945 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Huang, Ho-Yi - Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering and Materials Science, 1968-1974; 167946 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Huang, Wen H. - Geology, 1979-1981; 167949 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Huddle, Germaine Burchard - Sociology, 1977-1979; 167950 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hudson, Jack William - Biology, 1962-1967; 167951 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Huelsman, Lawrence P. - Electrical Engineering, 1964; 167952 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Hughes, Leo - English, 1961-1962; 167953 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Hungerford, Ed Vernon, III - Physics, 1969-1973; 167954 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Hunter, Daniel - Philosophy, 1979-1981; 167955 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Hurley, Patricia Ann - Political Science, 1984-1986; 167956 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Hyland, Richard P. - History, 1979-1982; 167957 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Hylarides, Mark D. - Chemistry, 1980-1981; 167958 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Iglesias, John H., Jr. - English, 1969-1973; 167959 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Innis, George Seth, Jr. - Mathematics, 1964; 167960 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Ip, Yuen-Kwong (Alex) - Biology, 1979-1980; 167961 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Isenberg, James Allen - Mathematics, 1983-1984; 167962 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Jackson, Kenneth Wayne - Sociology, 1981-1982; 167963 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Jackson, Roy - Chemical Engineering, 1965-1979; 167964 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Jaco, William Howard - Mathematics, 1970-1982; 167965 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Jacobowitz, Howard J. - Mathematics, 1971-1976; 167966 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Jacobs, Mark Q. - Mathematics, 1967-1968; 167967 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Jacobson, Barry - Chemistry, 1971-1972; 167968 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Jacobson, Marcus Jacob - Mechanical Engineering, 1961 [?]; 167969 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Jacquemont, Christiane - French, 1979; 167970 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Jaggi, R. K. - Space Science, 1970; 167971 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Jain, G. C. - Electrical Engineering, 1964-1967; 167972 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Jaksch, Hans - Economics, 1960-1964; 167973 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Jansen, Capt. Alan L. - Naval Science, 1972-1974; 167974 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Jansson, Birger - Mathematical Sciences, 1975; 167975 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Jenkins, James A. - Mathematics, 1962; 167976 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Jenner, Richard Allen - Economics, 1963-1965; 167977 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Jennings, Ross - Jones School of Administration, 1980-1981; 167978 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Jevons, Morris John - Electrical Engineering, 1961-1962; 167979 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Johnson, Dan M. - Biology, 1970-1976; 167980 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Johnson, David Lewis - Mathematics, 1980; 167981 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Johnson, Lt. Comdr. Francis Clinton, USN - Naval Science, 1964-1966; 167982 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Johnson, Gregory A. - Anthropology, 1972-1973; 167983 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Johnson, Guy, Jr. - Mathematics, 1954-1966; 167984 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Johnson, Kenneth D. - Mathematics, 1972-1973; 167985 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Johnson, Lawrence Todd - Accounting, 1970-1982; 167986 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Johnston, John Wallis - Commerce, 1962-1967; 167987 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Jones, Edward D. B. - Architecture, 1982; 167988 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Josephson, Ben, Jr. - Physics, 1961-1963; 167989 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Joynton, Olin - Philosophy, 1979-1980; 167990 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Justice, Blair - Sociology, 1967-1968; 167991 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Kahn, Edward B. - Psychology, 1979-1983; 167992 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Kane, William M. - Fine Arts, 1965-1966; 167993 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Kapadia, Asha Seth - Mathematical Sciences, 1977-1980; 167994 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Kaplan, Bert - Psychology, 1963-1964; 167995 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Kaplan, Howard B. - Sociology, 1977-1979; 167996 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Kapp, Robert Alexander - History, 1970-1972; 167997 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Karff, Joan - Health and Physical Education, 1978-1981; 167998 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Kazlow, Michael Lee - Mathematics, 1976-1978; 167999 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Kegley, Charles W. - Philosophy, 1964; 168000 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Kelly, Charles Ray - Architecture/Health Facilities Planning, 1974-1975; 168001 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Kelly, John Rains - Economics, 1973; 168002 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Kelly, Joseph Leonard, Jr. - Mechanical Engineering, 1962-1964; 168003 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Kelly, Thomas D. - English, 1967-1974; 168004 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Kelly, William A., Jr. - Economics and Accounting, 1975-1978; 168005 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Kendrick, Robert M. - Architecture, 1965-1967; 168006 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Kennedy, John Hines - Biomedical Engineering, 1969-1976; 168007 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Kenner, W. Hugh - History (declined offer), 1962; 168008 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Kennon, Paul A., Jr. - Architecture, 1964-1971; 168009 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy - Humanities, 1975; 168010 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Kerney, Charles Henry - Architecture, 1977-1982; 168011 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Kessick, Michael A. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1972-1976; 168012 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Kessler, Joachim - Physics, 1966-1967; 168013 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Kilper, Dennis John - Architecture, 1970-1975; 168014 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - King, John - Architecture, 1973-1975; 168015 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Kiperman, Anita - Spanish, 1972-1974; 168016 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Kiro, Schmuel - Mathematics, 1982-1984; 168223 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Klein, Douglas J. - Chemistry, 1979; 168224 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Knapp, Anthony W. - Mathematics, 1973; 168225 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Knowles, Lt. JG Charles E. - Naval Science, 1964 [?]; 168226 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Koehler, Herman Richard - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1980; 168227 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Koenig, Warren - Chemical Engineering, 1979-1980; 168228 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Kohler, Sigurd - Physics, 1965-1968; 168229 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Kotlow, Daniel Benjamin - Mathematics, 1972; 168230 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Kovar, Robert - Space Science, 1966-1968; 168231 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Krahl, Nat Wetzel - Civil Engineering and Architecture, 1957-1981; 168232 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Kraintz, Leon - Biology, 1964; 168233 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Krammer, Arnold - History, 1980-1982; 168234 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Kratzenstein, Klaus-Christhart - Shepherd School of Music, 1968-1975; 168235 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Krawitz, Aaron D. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1975-1980; 168236 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Kreuzer, Helmut - German, 1965-1966; 168237 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Kritzer, Herbert Morris - Political Science, 1975-1978; 168238 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Krumland, Rand B. - Administrative Sciences, 1977-1980; 168239 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Krzyzaniak, Marian - Economics, 1964-1981; 168240 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Kurland, Charles G. - Biochemistry, 1997; 168241 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Kuykendall, Carol B. - Education, 1972; 168242 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Labatut, Jean - Architecture, 1967; 168245 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Lacy, Bill Neal - Architecture, 1961-1965; 168246 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Lady, George M. - Economics, 1967; 168247 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - de Lancie, John - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1977; 168248 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Land, James - Economics, 1968-1976; 168249 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Lane, Anthony M. - Physics, 1965; 168250 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Lang, Friedrich G. - Religious Studies, 1971-1972; 168251 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Lanphier, Col. Paul H. - Military Science, 1963-1967; 168252 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Largay, James A., III - Economics and Accounting, 1971-1974; 168253 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Lasswell (Crist), Lynda - Jefferson Davis Papers, 1970-2013; 168254 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Latham, Gary V. - Geology, 1974-1975; 168255 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Lathrop, Barnes Fletcher - History, 1964; 168256 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Lauderdale, Martha A. - Spanish and French, 1960-1967; 168257 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Lawrie, Gerald M. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1980-1983; 168258 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Lawton, Wayne M. - Mathematics, 1972-1974; 168259 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Leach, William J. - Civil Engineering, 1980-1982; 168260 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lear, Floyd Seyward - History, 1925-1974; 168261 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - LeCompte, Margaret Diane - Sociology, 1978; 168262 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lecuyer, Maurice A. - French, 1962-1979; 168263 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Lee, Thomas W., Jr. - Biology, 1964-1965; 168264 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Legenhausen, Gary C. - Philosophy, 1980; 168265 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Legg, David - Health and Physical Education, 1979-1980; 168266 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Legg, James C. - Physics, 1963-1967; 168267 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Lehnert, Herbert Hermann - German, 1958-1967; 168268 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Leifeste, A. A., Jr. - Architecture, 1947-1973; 168269 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Leiter, Kenneth C. - Sociology, 1971-1978; 168270 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Lentricchia, Frank - English, 1982-1983; 168271 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Lentricchia, Melissa - English, 1982-1984; 168272 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Lert, Richard Johannes - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1980; 168273 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Levine, Edward P. - Political Science, 1972-1975; 168274 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Levy, Allan H. - Mathematical Sciences, 1971-1975; 168275 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Lewis, Hanna B. - Germanics, 1962-1965; 168276 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Lewis, Robert - Art and Art History, 1981-1982; 168277 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Lewis, William S. - German and Russian, 1981; 168278 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Liemohn, Wendell Philip - Health and Physical Education (photograph), 1963-1964; 168279 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Lindsey, Cdr. James - Naval Science, 1984; 168280 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Lintz, Bernadette C. - French and Italian, 1981-1983; 168281 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Livingston, Charles - Mathematics, 1980-1981; 168282 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Livingston, Stephen E. - Health and Physical Education, 1980-1981; 168283 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Loevinsohn, Ernest - Philosophy, 1977-1980; 168284 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Lohwater, A. J. - Mathematics, 1959-1965; 168285 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Long, Chalmers G., Jr. - Architecture, 1969-1976; 168286 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Lopez-Morales, Humberto - Spanish, 1968-1973; 168287 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Lord, Tom F. - Architecture, 1971-1983; 168288 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Louis, Andrew - Germanics, 1946-1967; 168289 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Lovesey, Stephen W. - Physics, 1977-1979; 168290 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Low, Frank James - Space Science, 1966-1979; 168291 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Low, Myron J. - History, 1965-1966; 168292 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Lowe, Alma Louise - English/Dean of Women, 1962-1967; 168293 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Lowe, Pardee J. - German, 1965-1966; 168294 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Lucas, Henry F. - Biology and Geology, 1964-1965; 168295 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Lucas, Therese - Architecture, 1974-1976; 168296 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Lucas, Timothy S. - Accounting, 1976-1979; 168297 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Lusty, Arthur H., Jr. - Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering and Materials Science (offer not accepted), 1967-1968; 168298 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Lutfiyya, Abdulla M. - Sociology, 1967-1968; 168299 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Lyne, William Henry - Electrical Engineering, 1963-1965; 168300 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Lynn, M. Stuart - Mathematical Sciences/Director of the Institute of Computer Services and Applications, 1971-1976; 168301 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Lytz, Walter R. - Campus Business Office, 1964-1974 [?]; 168302 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - MacDougall, David Cook - Fine Arts, 1970-1975; 168303 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Mackey, Louis H. - Philosophy, 1959-1968; 168304 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Mackey, Louis H. (and his son's haircut) vs. Lamar High School, 1965; 168305 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Mackey, William Sturges, Jr. - Business Administration, 1946-1963; 168306 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Mackenzie, Donald C. - Classics, 1960-1968 [?]; 168307 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - MacLane, Gerald Robinson - Mathematics, 1943-1964; 168308 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Macve, Richard H. - Accounting, 1982-1983; 168309 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Magrino, Frank - Economics, 1972-1973; 168310 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Maguire, John Joseph - Space Science, 1966; 168311 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Maley, Sharon H. - Psychology, 1980-1981; 168762 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mandelbrojt, Szden - Mathematics, 1927, 1941-1965; 168763 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Manns, Suzanne - Art, 1977; 168764 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Markey, Eugene T. - Commerce, 1961-1966, 1969-1976; 168765 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Marks, Scott - Mathematical Sciences, 1979-1982; 168766 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Marsak, Leonard Mendes - History, 1960-1965; 168767 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Marsh, Thad Norton - English/Assistant to the President, 1952-1962; 168768 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Martens, Stanley - Philosophy, 1979; 168769 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Martin, David W. - Sociology, 1980; 168770 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Martin, R. Russell - Biomedical Engineering, 1977-1982; 168771 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Maschler, Michael - Mathematical Sciences, 1972; 168772 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Masterson, William Henry - History/Dean of Humanities, 1948-1966; 168773 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mather, Michael - Mathematics, 1967-1968; 168775 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Matson, Jack V. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1973-1974; 168776 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Mattson, Joan C. - Biomedical Engineering, 1982-1983; 168777 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Mayersak, Joseph R. - Mechanical Engineering, 1965; 168778 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - McCaleb, Thomas S. - Economics, 1977-1980; 168779 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - McCallum, Bennett T. - Economics, 1964; 168780 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - McCarthy, Robert Joseph - Physics, 1966-1967; 168781 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - McCarty, Mark - Fine Arts, 1975-1976; 168782 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - McClain, William M. - Chemistry, 1982; 168793 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - McCleary, Thompson - Architecture, 1961; 168794 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - McClelland, Franklin N. - Accounting, 1974-1979; 168795 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - McCord, William M. - Sociology, 1965-1968; 168796 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - McDaniel, John - Architecture, 1976-1978; 168797 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - McDonald, A. P. - Engineering Graphics/Manager of Printing and Reproduction, 1954-1973; 168798 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - McElroy, Bernard P., Jr. - English, 1978, 1981-1982; 168799 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - McEnany, Michael Vincent, Jr. - Electrical Engineering/Dean of Undergraduate Affairs, 1943-1974; 168800 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - McGinnis, Rodney W. - Psychology, 1967-1972; 168801 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - McLure, Charles E. - Economics, 1965-1979; 168802 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - McMahon, Kathryn K. - French, 1972-1973; 168803 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - McManaway, James Gilmer - English, 1966; 168804 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - McMurry, John E. - Chemistry, 1977; 168805 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - McNeill, I. E. - Accounting, n.d.; 168806 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - McPhail, Malcolm Ross - Electrical Engineering, 1961-1973; 168807 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Mears, Herbert R. - Fine Arts, 1965-1966; 168808 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Meegan, Charles A. - Physics, 1974-1975; 168809 (Box 7, Folder 37)